Hello,
I'm Prashant and I'm
building Strike.
AI-run options vault for
tokenized stocks where the
AI can't break your
rules.
Now,
stock tokens are arriving
on chain starting with
Robinhood chain,
but holding them earns
nothing extra.
Covered call funds made
that a hundred billion
dollar category off chain.
Now in Strike,
an AI agent picks
the strike each week,
but the smart contract
enforces the depositors'
rule.
If the AI agent
breaks them,
it is rejected and
its own bond pays
the depositors.
It's live on two
testnets with real option
sales and a real
slash and over 1,500
tests.
And we are working
on to make it
to arrive to mainnet.
And that is why
we would like you
to fund our company
and our waitlist is
open today.
So let's check out
Strike.